Oh no, I'm gonna be late!
[Anzu] Wait. What did I just say?
That phrase… It sounded so familiar.
[yelps]
[Hijiri] She's the one
who went running out into the street
right in front of us.
ONE WAY STREET
[officer] Please, miss,
be more aware of your surroundings.
[soft chuckle]
[Tsuchiya]
Let us give you a ride to school.
[car door closes]
[Anzu]
It seems like a pretty expensive car.
[car door closes]
Hey, um, I'm really sorry
that I made you late.
Having a couple of tardies?
That won't affect my report card.
I'm an excellent student.
[Anzu] Anyway,
why would a rich kid like him
go to a public school?
He's good-looking
but I haven't seen him before.
Well, you must be ecstatic.
I mean, getting the chance
to ride to school with me and everything.
[Hijiri] You should be grateful.
[grunts]
[Anzu in deep voice] Hang on, Anzu,
don't punch him in the face.
Hold it in. This all happened
because I was being careless.
[in normal voice]
Oh. Both Kazuki and Saki messaged me.
TSUKASA: YOU GOOD?
I should respond.
I GOT IN A MINOR ACCIDENT,
BUT I'M OKAY.
[theme music]
[school bell dings]
#7: WHAT A STRONG PERSONALITY
[indistinct chatter]
[Anzu] Great, just in time for break.
Uh, this is me right here.
[Hijiri] You exchanged contacts
with Tsuchiya, right?
Hmm?
-[Tsuchiya] My name is Tsuchiya.
-Oh, yeah.
[Hijiri] I'll be in touch at a later day.
You just wait.
And enjoy dreaming about me.
[Anzu] Seriously?
There's still more to talk about?
-Hmm?
-[gasps]
Oh…
Anzu! Why did you arrive
with Mr. Hijiri Koganei?
Mister?
Anzu, are… are you sure
that you're not hurt?
Yeah, thank you, Saki.
[gasps]
You are so lucky!
-[exclaims]
-You got hit by Mr. Hijiri's car.
[Anzu] Why do you keep saying "Mister"?
What do you mean?
He's Mr. Hijiri Koganei,
the rich star from Class 8!
He is like a prince.
He even has his own fan club.
PRINCE HIJIRI
I see…
[Anzu] I mean, it seems obvious,
but, this has got to be
another one of their setups!
-[Anzu] I got to get up…
-And insert!
-[Anzu] I'll be late…
-Now she'll be running really late!
-[Makoto] Hosshi!
-[Junta] Anzu!
Oh!
-Are you okay? We heard you got hit!
-Anzu, I was worried about you.
[in high-pitched voice]
Hayami! Oh gosh!
-You're not hurt at all, are you?
-Nope. I'm all good.
[sighs]
I bet you were rushing
and ran into the street.
Yeah.
Still, I really think
you should go to the hospital.
The car barely hit me, though.
Hosshi, you and Hayami are friends?
Nice!
He's, um, he's an "old friend,"
quote unquote.
-Let's go.
-[squeals]
Let me know if anything starts hurting,
all right?
[Anzu] Okay, thanks.
[sighs]
This is so incredibly unfair,
I can't even…
Both of those heartthrobs are just
so worried about you.
Well, actually,
Kazuki wasn't worried about me at all.
A FEW DAYS LATER.
[Anzu] Maybe I'm a little early.
[Tsuchiya] Would this coming Saturday
work for you?
[Anzu] What else is left to go over?
[car approaching]
[Hijiri scoffs]
You're extremely early.
You wanted to see me so bad
you've been waiting here since last night?
You really are something else, aren't you?
[forced laugh]
Oh yeah, I've been waiting all night.
Held strong,
like I was defending the Alamo.
Whatever.
What's with the peasant look
you've got on?
[Hijiri] How could you even stand
next to me dressed like that?
Are you trying to insult me?
-[angry meow]
-[grunts]
[Anzu] I humbly apologize.
I'm just a low-born villager NPC
in a game, repeating the same line
over and over again.
VILLAGER A
[scoffs]
Whatever.
-[Hijiri] Get in.
-Huh?
[yelps]
[groans]
-You lack sincerity.
-[growls]
With all my attention,
you'll be our school's Cinderella.
[Anzu] Wanted:
Someone to translate for this guy.
[Anzu] Well…
[magical music]
-What the heck am I doing here?
-Aah…
Hmm. Now you're decent.
And now I wanna know what's happening.
-Get her some flat shoes.
-[approaching footsteps]
[Hijiri] Why are you unnecessarily tall?
Maybe I should give you
some of my height, then.
-[Hijiri] Okay, let's go to lunch.
-Huh? Whoa, wait, what?
Go to lunch, why?
[Hijiri] I'm really pushed for time here.
-Tell me what's going on!
-We're doing French.
[groans]
I don't need lunch!
I don't get why you think it's okay
to make me over like that!
It's entirely your fault
for showing up on a date with me
dressed like a poor being.
What are you talking about, date?
Aren't we meeting 'cause I got hit?
No need to play dumb.
You purposefully got hit
in order to get closer to me, right?
Huh?
Cars are legally at fault
when they hit pedestrians.
You took advantage of that
so you could go out with me, didn't you?
You actually think
that I staged the accident?
-Oh, did you not?
-Not at all, no!
Idiots like that exist?
It's happened countless times
since preschool.
So several exist, then.
Tsuchiya's driver's license is
on a permanent watchlist now.
[Tsuchiya] It was suspended once too.
[Anzu] You poor thing.
I'm really, really sorry!
Anyway, I'm not one of those girls, and I,
I can't accept these clothes.
I'll pay for them.
Nine hundred dollars, just for the dress.
[yelps]
Is it made out of an ancient relic silk
or something?
YOU OBTAINED ANCIENT THREADS!
Whatever.
Intentional or no,
it was still an accident.
You received clothes and you're also
about to have lunch with me.
Think of it as a peasant's godsend.
[groaning]
[Anzu] Mr. Tsuchiya, please stop.
What now?
I feel bad
that you did all of this for me.
-Whoa? Huh?
-[accessories jingle]
I'm not at all interested in you.
[gasps]
[Anzu] So there's no need for us
to waste each other's time.
See ya.
[retreating footsteps]
[Anzu] Being manipulated
by an extremely full of himself rich kid
is really annoying,
especially when he's got
a stuck-up attitude like that.
But the most frustrating thing is
he actually thought
I was one of those idiots
who would stage an accident for a date!
[men laughing]
[Anzu in deep voice] I belong
to a warrior race that forges its way down
the exact opposite path of life
every single day!
[screams, heavy breathing]
[Anzu] Damn, my pits are sweating
all over this 900-dollar dress.
THIS IS A ROMANTIC ANIME
She has no interest in me?
[birds chirping]
HIJIRI LOVE
-That's not good. Mr. Hijiri looks sad.
-[girls swooning]
But he looks so fragile and beautiful.
[approaching footsteps]
Huh?
Hijiri Koganei.
Uh, it's you.
Address me respectfully. That was rude.
[sighs]
Are you kidding me?
[scoffs]
What do you want anyway?
Trying to make up
for being rude the other day?
[Anzu] I dry-cleaned the clothes,
so I just wanted to return them to you.
Goodbye.
[retreating footsteps]
[Hijiri] She certainly left in a hurry
after going out of her way
to return the gifts I gave her.
There's no need
to worry about that peasant.
But the way she's been giving me
all of that attitude…
[sinister music]
[Hijiri] I don't like it one bit.
Tsuchiya, I need something investigated.
[cheerful music]
[Junta humming]
Junta, you're chipper.
Wednesday means no club,
so I get to walk home with you.
Oh, okay, I see.
Kazuki has work today, right?
Yeah. What should we do for dinner?
It might be terrible,
but I can make us something.
Really? You would? I'll eat it!
You know, maybe I should learn
how to cook myself.
I only know how to make ramen.
You should just focus on your baseball.
[Anzu] He's such a good guy
compared to that other one.
I hope Junta finds happiness
with someone he truly loves.
But for that to happen,
I really need to do something about them.
-[Riri] Anzu!
-[blows air]
I wanna come too! Can I come for dinner?
[Anzu] Maybe I should just give her
a quick death.
[Anzu] Honestly, how dare you?
Why send such a ridiculous character?
There's no way I'd fall for him!
Oh, when I'm in this form,
everybody can see and hear us.
[giggles]
Well, I'm not a very good cook,
so you should probably just go home.
-Not letting go of that grip, then?
-Hmm?
[Junta] Uh…
-[car door opens]
-[both] Huh?
Anzu Hoshino.
-Not him.
-[chuckles]
You're the first woman to say
that you have no interest in me at all.
I'm intrigued.
Just know
that I'll steal your heart eventually.
-Heh.
-[squeals]
-Aren't you starving?
-Mm-hm.
-[Riri] Oh, jeez. My stomach just rumbled…
-Goodness. Such a cramped place.
-Oh! So, Junta…
-I'm sure it is for you, Mr. Prince.
-[Hijiri] By the way, who are these two?
-[both] Huh?
[Hijiri] My business is only with Hoshino.
[Junta sighs]
I'm Riri, Anzu's cousin.
And this is one of her oldest friends
from childhood, Junta.
The three of us will be having dinner
together tonight.
You can actually leave now.
So…
What's this business?
Some more lame stuff?
[Hijiri] Tsuchiya.
Yes, sir.
-Huh? Hmm…
-Miss Hoshino, this is for you.
[Anzu] Huh?
[Anzu] It's a Skitch! And a VR headset!
The chocolates are all fancy brands!
[squealing]
-[Tsuchiya] And that's not all, miss.
-Huh?
[Anzu yelps]
-[meowing]
-[Anzu whimpers]
[Anzu] Destruction level: severe.
[meowing]
Well, you appear
to be satisfied with my gifts.
[Anzu] That came out of nowhere.
Did he actually feel bad
about me getting upset?
Along with great elegance
and my appearance which exudes charm,
I have the financial power
to make your every wish come true.
[gasps]
You're interested in me now, right?
Oh, so it's that kind of scenario.
Tell me, how did you find out
about my favorite things?
Anything's possible for me.
No, an actual answer.
[Anzu] It really bothered you when I said
I wasn't interested in you, didn't it?
[Anzu grunts]
-[in deep voice] Well, guess what? Hey!
-Stop right there!
Anzu, hon, I just need
a quick word with you for a second!
I know that we confiscated
your three greatest desires,
but it would be very rude
of you to reject his gifts.
I will allow 'em,
but here's the catch for accepting them!
What, are you serious?
You can only keep 'em
if you allow a relationship
to develop with Hijiri Koganei.
[sighs]
-[Anzu] If I start dating him…
-[arrogant laughter]
…I can enjoy all those gifts right now.
[kittens meowing]
What are those two
talking about out there?
Who… who knows?
[sighs]
Um, your name was Koganei?
That's informal and rude.
Oh, sorry, Mr. Koganei.
I heard about the accident
with Anzu and everything.
But, um, well, do you, um…
[Junta] Anzu, uh, do you like her?
Like her?
That's not an emotion
I'd feel for anyone at all.
That's an emotion
everyone else feels for me.
Right.
But Hoshino's stated
that she has absolutely no interest in me.
It's a serious matter.
[Junta] I see.
That's why you're doing all this.
Just so you know, Anzu won't become
your friend just because…
you're rich or you're good-looking.
Hmm?
[slaps]
[Anzu] You're completely clueless
about humans.
Setting up forced encounters
and messing with emotions,
now luring me in with my desires.
I'm no fool.
Oh.
-Please leave. I don't want this stuff.
-How could…
[Anzu] I'm incredibly sorry
if I hurt your pride,
but you'll have to find someone else
to fawn over you.
And since you're human,
you understand feelings.
Right, Hijiri?
[Anzu] And another thing,
there's no point strutting around
promising my every wish
with your parents' money.
It's okay when it's money
you earn yourself.
And above all…
If you don't have Momohiki,
then you don't have a chance!
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[huffs, sighs]
That was interesting.
Junta…
[Anzu]
If I had accepted Riri's conditions,
would they have released Junta
from the love spell?
[exhales sharply]
I'm sorry you're involved with this.
Don't be. I'm just fine.
If you're ever in trouble,
please just let me know.
[whimpers]
[Anzu] He's too good of a person
it's painful.
[chuckles]
Hey Anzu, how come
you're playing with him anyway?
Yeah, I won't let you play my new game.
What? You suck.
-[Junta] Uh, are you sure?
-It's okay. Those guys are all talk.
And I had plans to hang with you first.
How come you kicked him out, huh?
I really want to kick you out.
-[Riri] Not nice!
-[chuckles]
DONUTS
[rustling]
[sighs]
[manager] Miss Hoshino,
we've got a new employee starting today.
Oh, right.
[Anzu] What?
[manager] This is Mr. Koganei.
[bright music]
Yes, I'm here to learn.
You should have no issues.
CONBINI MART
SEASONAL SWEETS
Welcome in.
I appreciate that.
Come again.
Hey!
How many meters above us are you?
Excuse you, millions of meters.
Orbitally higher?
You think that's good customer service?
She's right.
It's better if you add,
"But I won't actually wait for you"
after "Come again."
[Anzu]
Don't encourage the hot and cold thing!
Manager, sir, are you sure about this?
Hmm, well, thing is…
[device beeps]
-Shall I warm it?
-Oh, yes.
[manager] The customers all seem
to be attracted to Mr. Koganei's aura,
so there haven't been any complaints.
[Anzu]
But he's inconsiderate and obnoxious!
Hijiri went viral,
known as the convenience store prince.
The #storeprince spread
like wildfire all over social media…
SEASONAL SWEETS NOW AVAILABLE
…and attracted a whole lot of customers!
[customers whispering]
Mm-hm.
AVAILABLE NATIONWIDE
Your change. Do come again.
Thanks.
[Anzu grumbles]
[Anzu] I guess he must've ended up
with that attitude
because everyone around him
seems to enable him.
But he is a fast learner,
and he doesn't ask for time off.
-And to be honest, he does work hard.
-Welcome in.
-You can take your break now.
-Mm-hm.
[chuckles]
Wait, is the Prince going on break?
Sorry about that.
[chuckles awkwardly]
CONBINI MART
[moans]
I'm so tired.
Oh, Mr. Tsuchiya.
Good evening, miss.
Hi there. Hijiri will be out in a sec.
Miss Hoshino.
I don't know how to express the gratitude
I have for what you have done.
What?
Mr. Hijiri, he attended an expensive
escalator-styled private school,
but due to his father's wishes,
he was enrolled at the school
where you currently attend.
Oh.
[Tsuchiya] His loved ones
are enamored with him,
and he always got anything
and everything he wanted growing up,
so he can be a bit out of touch,
and he lacks common sense.
Hmm…
His father became concerned about that,
so he decided that he wanted Hijiri
to experience a normal life
at a normal school.
[Tsuchiya] However, his innate
and inherent heir of nobility
has always made him feel
above everything normal.
Right.
But now, because you had the ability
to reason with him directly…
First, I hit the bottom right key there.
And then I enter…
[Tsuchiya] Mr. Hijiri has actually been
trying to learn more about normal life.
This is all your doing.
Thank you so very much.
Oh, of course.
[chuckles]
NARIKIN BANK
BANK ACCOUNT
ORDINARY FINANCIALS
[squeals, gasps]
My paycheck!
I'm so glad. How should I spend it? Hmm…
[chuckles]
-[Hijiri] Hoshino.
-[gasps]
[shrieks]
Jeez, Hijiri!
There's no work today, is there?
Then why are you following me?
How rude. I just happened to see you
so I called your name.
I received my paycheck today.
So, Hoshino, what do you want?
Huh?
It's only a few days' worth
so it can't be too great,
but I'm sure I can fulfill anything
your peasant heart desires.
And I earned the money all on my own.
But don't get the wrong idea.
[Hijiri chuckles dryly]
It's not like
I did any of this stuff for you.
[Anzu] That hot and cold personality
was implanted in him.
What do you want?
-A bag? Some shoes?
-No, no, thanks.
-Some jewelry?
-No, no, no, no.
Instead of a gift,
would you prefer a date?
Please, shut up!
[Anzu] As much as I want to say
I don't want a thing from him…
[soft piano music]
Hmm.
Oh! All right, I know what I want.
[Anzu chuckles]
What in the world is that?
Pipiko. You wouldn't know.
It was surprisingly cheap,
even for a peasant's item.
-[snaps]
-Hmm?
[Anzu] Here. That's your half.
Thank you for the treat.
[chuckles]
You're happy with something like this?
Well yeah, I think it's the perfect thing
to share with friends.
[exclaims]
What do you think?
It tastes artificial and cheap.
But it's, it's not bad.
[magical music]
[gasps]
[yelps, grunts]
What's wrong?
Getting back my sanity. That's all.
[Anzu grunts]
[Anzu]
This might have been a huge mistake.
[scrubbing]
[door opens]
I'm home, guys.
[phone chimes, vibrates]
What?
ARISA
CAN WE MEET?
[Anzu] It's Kazuki's phone.
ARISA
CAN WE MEET?
[Anzu gasps]
It's a girl!
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪